from unicodedata import category

question_data = [

        {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "In the 1988 film 'Akira' and Tetsuo ends up destroying Tokyo.", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "Clefairy was intended to be Ash starting Poke"
                     "mon in the pilot episode of the cartoon.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "In Kill La Kill, the weapon of the main protagonist is a katana. ", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "The anime 'Lucky Star' follows the story of one girl who is unaware she is God.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "No Game No Life first aired in 2014.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "Gosho Aoyama Made This Series: (Detective Conan / Case Closed!)", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "In Pokemon, Ash's Pikachu refuses to go into a pokeball.", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "The name of the attack 'Kamehameha';"
                     " in Dragon Ball Z was named after a famous king of Hawaii.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "Kiznaiver is an adaptation of a manga.", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "In Chobits, Hideki found Chii in his apartment.", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]

